{"_default": {"1": {"id": 1, "question_body": "1+1", "choices": [{"choice_body": "2", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "3"}, {"choice_body": "4"}, {"choice_body": "5"}], "tags": ["test"]}, "2": {"id": 2, "question_body": "2+2", "choices": [{"choice_body": "4", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "5"}, {"choice_body": "6"}, {"choice_body": "7"}], "tags": ["test"]}, "3": {"id": 3, "question_body": "what is your name", "choices": [{"choice_body": "bin"}, {"choice_body": "bb"}, {"choice_body": "cc", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "aa"}], "tags": ["test"]}, "4": {"id": 4, "question_body": "asdf", "choices": [{"choice_body": "asdf"}, {"choice_body": "asdf"}, {"choice_body": "asdf"}, {"choice_body": "asdf", "is_answer": 1}], "tags": ["test"]}, "5": {"id": 5, "question_body": "What's the sum of degrees of all angles in a triangle?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "90"}, {"choice_body": "180", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "270"}, {"choice_body": "360"}], "tags": ["maths"]}, "7": {"id": 7, "question_body": "What is a hectare?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "10 000 square meters", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "1000 square meters"}, {"choice_body": "1000 meters"}, {"choice_body": "100 000 square meters"}], "tags": ["maths"]}, "8": {"id": 8, "question_body": "x=13. what is 5x", "choices": [{"choice_body": "65", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "513"}, {"choice_body": "39"}, {"choice_body": "52"}], "tags": ["maths"]}, "9": {"id": 9, "question_body": "What is perpendicular?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "diagonal lines"}, {"choice_body": "vertical lines"}, {"choice_body": "parrallel lines"}, {"choice_body": "lines that meet at 90 degrees", "is_answer": 1}], "tags": ["maths"]}, "10": {"id": 10, "question_body": "What is 0.7 in percentages?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "70 percent", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "7 percent"}, {"choice_body": "0.7 percent"}, {"choice_body": "0.07 percent"}], "tags": ["maths"]}, "11": {"id": 11, "question_body": "what's my name", "choices": [{"choice_body": "b"}, {"choice_body": "c"}, {"choice_body": "d"}, {"choice_body": "e", "is_answer": 1}], "tags": ["test"]}, "12": {"id": 12, "question_body": "what's my name", "choices": [{"choice_body": "b"}, {"choice_body": "c"}, {"choice_body": "d"}, {"choice_body": "e", "is_answer": 1}], "tags": ["test"]}, "13": {"id": 13, "question_body": "What does ailment mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "sickness", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "colour"}, {"choice_body": "type of bird"}, {"choice_body": "cure"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "15": {"id": 15, "question_body": "What does scanty mean", "choices": [{"choice_body": "scarce", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "song"}, {"choice_body": "robber"}, {"choice_body": "full"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "16": {"id": 16, "question_body": "What does lubricate mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "to make things more slippery", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "oil"}, {"choice_body": "soap"}, {"choice_body": "machine"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "17": {"id": 17, "question_body": "What does cajole mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "persuade", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "animal"}, {"choice_body": "thief"}, {"choice_body": "fruit"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "18": {"id": 18, "question_body": "What is a podiatrist?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "foot doctor", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "child doctor"}, {"choice_body": "surgeon"}, {"choice_body": "skin doctor"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "19": {"id": 19, "question_body": "What does gale mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "strong wind", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "animal"}, {"choice_body": "animal food"}, {"choice_body": "building"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "20": {"id": 20, "question_body": "What does conventional mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "usual", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "easy"}, {"choice_body": "convenient"}, {"choice_body": "exceptional"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "21": {"id": 21, "question_body": "What does introverted mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "keeping to yourself", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "inside a house"}, {"choice_body": "a break between activities"}, {"choice_body": "complete"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "22": {"id": 22, "question_body": "What does spontaneous mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "unplanned", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "spotty"}, {"choice_body": "barrel"}, {"choice_body": "none of the others"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "23": {"id": 23, "question_body": "What does interlude mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "intrude"}, {"choice_body": "time between activities", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "person who likes to eat apples"}, {"choice_body": "person who likes to eat pears"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "24": {"id": 24, "question_body": "What does deplorable mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "unfortunate", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "detergent"}, {"choice_body": "(please insert answer)"}, {"choice_body": "adventurous"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "25": {"id": 25, "question_body": "What does repulsive mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "disgusting", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "pulsing"}, {"choice_body": "repeated"}, {"choice_body": "attractive"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "26": {"id": 26, "question_body": "What does extroverted mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "interested in people", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "outside"}, {"choice_body": "from the outer layer"}, {"choice_body": "free"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "27": {"id": 27, "question_body": "What does fatal mean?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "deadly", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "fat"}, {"choice_body": "loving"}, {"choice_body": "eventual"}], "tags": ["english"]}, "28": {"id": 28, "question_body": "Who is Arthur Phillip?", "choices": [{"choice_body": "first governer os NSW", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "first governer os NSW", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "first governer os NSW", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "first governer os NSW", "is_answer": 1}], "tags": ["english"]}, "31": {"choices": [{"choice_body": "comedy"}, {"choice_body": "sickness"}, {"choice_body": "cure, fix", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "type of food"}], "id": 14, "question_body": "What does remedy mean?", "tags": ["english"]}, "32": {"choices": [{"choice_body": "pile"}, {"choice_body": "small amount ", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "block"}, {"choice_body": "stain"}], "id": 6, "question_body": "What does smidge mean????", "tags": ["english"]}, "34": {"choices": [{"choice_body": "1"}, {"choice_body": "2"}, {"choice_body": "3", "is_answer": 1}, {"choice_body": "4"}], "id": 29, "question_body": "test 01", "tags": ["english", "test"]}}}